hey you big dumb idiots we got the grand
prize the Predator statue come collect
it show me where is it are you blind
it's right there
baby it's real it's legit great come on
out
individually how stupid do you think we
are you can see it's your dumbass friend
dressed
up is that a falor car oh yeah yeah yeah
it is we made it ourselves we're
thinking of taking a photos and put it
on Pinterest just like do it yourself
it's like you can also do this if you
have the time and the willpower what's
the deal you big never- Ending Story fan
it's a good movie what does a rock biter
bite rocks that's a cool tattoo it looks
like uh like a gigantic gaping butthole
unique you're a unique
person you guys like drag racing right
we've been known to drift how about we
race for pink slips you win you get the
foul car we win you guys just bounce on
out of here and then sort of admit that
I'm the most atray looking dude you've
ever met great deal let's do it
okay
red you would have my job that's right
and it would only take me 5 years to
take it impressed why would I hire
someone who wants to take my job Bo I'm
smarter than I look and I know that I
look pretty smart I'm not sure I get
that exactly hey guys still in the
middle of this I get that I totally do
but we got to race these movie buff so
they're going to knock out our teeth out
I think I'll be leaving now hey h don't
make me kiss your asses let's
go I think I'll be staying now but if I
gave you a Wesley mask help us
Jersey As You
Wish first one pass the fence bro that's
right luck dragon's about to be mine
baby all right wait what's he talking
about okay on Jenny's go okay
[Music]
Jenny speed bumps they're not just for
hockey
[Music]
anymore woo yeah that was cool right
that worked oh yes that was the most
interesting interview I have ever been a
part
of I'm
fresh you got you got you got got be